taggedmail.com 2011-06-23

# Tagged - Terms of Service

Jump to Privacy Policy

## Terms of Service

Updated as of September 28, 2010

Please read the following important Terms of Service Agreement (the "Agreement") before accessing or using any of the various services (the "Services") made available to you (the "Member") by Tagged through http://www.tagged.com ("Tagged"). ONLY USERS WHO ARE 13 YEARS OF AGE OR OLDER MAY REGISTER FOR TAGGED. By completing the registration process for the Tagged website, you represent that you are 13 years of age or older, and can and will be legally bound by this Agreement. If you are a minor, your parent or guardian must read and accept the terms of this Agreement before you register. No Member may participate where doing so would be prohibited by any applicable law or regulation.

### A) Modifications

Tagged reserves the right to modify or amend this Agreement at any time, for any reason, or for no reason at all, at Tagged's sole discretion. The most recent version of this Agreement will be posted on the Tagged website. Although Tagged will provide notice of material changes to this Agreement on the Tagged website, as a Member it is your sole responsibility to keep yourself apprised of any such modifications or amendments. Should Member object to any terms and conditions of the Agreement or any subsequent modifications thereto or become dissatisfied with Tagged in any way, Member's only recourse is to immediately: (1) discontinue use of Tagged; (2) terminate Tagged registration; and (3) notify Tagged of termination.

### B) Description of Services

As a Member, you will be provided with a variety of services, as described on the Tagged website (the "Services"). Members may also utilize certain additional services offered from time to time such as shopping and e-commerce offerings and various informational services. Tagged reserves the right to enhance, modify, or discontinue the Services, in whole or in part, at any time, for any reason, or for no reason at all, at Tagged's sole discretion, with or without notice to Members, and with no obligation to Members.

### C) Member Conduct

Use of the Services by you, as Member, is subject to all applicable local, state, national and international laws and regulations. Tagged reserves the right, but does not assume any obligation, to monitor the Services to enforce this Agreement. Nor does Tagged guarantee that any monitoring it does perform will be to the Member's satisfaction. Upon learning of any violation of this Agreement, Tagged, at its sole discretion, may terminate your access to and use of the Services, require you to remedy such violation, and/or take any other actions that Tagged deems appropriate to enforce its rights and pursue all available remedies. Without limitation, Tagged reserves the right to terminate your access to and use of the Services if, in our view, your conduct fails to meet any of the following guidelines:

  1. Members shall not engage in any activity that constitutes harassment, including, but not limited to, excessive repetition when listing a person as a referral.
  2. Members shall not list the email addresses of people unknown to them.
  3. Members shall not list as referrals any email addresses that are fake, fictitious, or made up.
  4. Members shall not list as referrals any email addresses which are owned by or belong to that member.
  5. Members shall not attempt to interfere with any other person's use of the Services.
  6. Members shall not misrepresent their identity or impersonate any person.
  7. Members shall not hold themselves out as sponsored by, endorsed by, or affiliated with the Tagged website.
  8. Members shall not use any portion of the Tagged website or the Services for uploading, posting, emailing, transmitting or otherwise making available junk mail, commercial advertisements, or any other form of commercial solicitation.
  9. Members shall not use any portion of the Tagged website or the Services for uploading, posting, emailing, transmitting or otherwise making available content, including user names and friend list names, that is harmful, threatening, abusive, vulgar, obscene, profane, defamatory, libelous, hateful, or racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable.
  10. Members shall not use any portion of the Tagged website or the Services to post, share, promote and/or exchange  Content Harmful to Minors.
  11. Members shall not create Groups and/or post discussion comments in Groups that advocate, contain, depict, encourage, promote or solicit  Content Harmful to Minors.
  12. Members shall not upload photos, graphics or other content that contain or promote illegal substances or activities, including, but not limited to, underage drinking or smoking, substance abuse, weapon use, or gang affiliation.
  13. Members shall not post content that displays pornographic or sexually explicit material of any kind.
  14. Members shall not provide material that exploits people under the age of 18 in a sexual or violent manner, or solicits personal information from anyone under 18.
  15. Members shall not provide instructional information about illegal activities such as making or buying illegal weapons, violating someone's privacy, or providing or creating computer viruses.
  16. Members shall not attempt to gain unauthorized access to Tagged's database or other computer systems.
  17. Members shall not attempt to modify, translate, adapt, edit, decompile, disassemble, or reverse engineer any software programs used by Tagged in connection with the Tagged website or the Services.
  18. Members shall not engage in any activity that disrupts, diminishes the quality of, interferes with the performance of, or impairs the functionality of, the Services or the Tagged website.
  19. Members shall not use any portion of the Tagged website or the Services for any unlawful purpose.

All judgments concerning the applicability of these guidelines shall be at the sole and exclusive discretion of Tagged. Tagged will remove the offending material and alert the member against repeating the offense. If another direct violation of our Terms of Agreement is committed, a member's account will be fully terminated. A member is not necessarily offered a warning. An account may be terminated at any time, without notice, depending on the severity of the offense. 

### D) Privacy

Tagged has established a Privacy Policy to explain to Members how their information is collected and used, which Member can read by clicking http://www.Tagged.com/terms_of_service.html?priv=y#privacy_policy. Member's use of the Tagged website or the Services signifies acknowledgment of and agreement to Tagged's Privacy Policy. Members further acknowledge and agree that Tagged may disclose Member's personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, enforce this Agreement, or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Tagged, its employees, users and third parties, and the public, or as otherwise described in the Privacy Policy. The Add Friends feature is an easy way for Tagged users to invite friends through email. The email address(es) that you supply to use this service will only be used to send invitations to connect with you on Tagged.

### E) Document Retention Schedule

All personal information collected by Tagged in connection with your use of the Tagged website, including, without limitation, your name, location, email address, pictures, friend connections, messages, comments, login information, ip addresses and other data, will be stored by Tagged indefinitely in a safe and secure manner.

### F) Notice Regarding Commercial Email

MEMBERS CONSENT TO RECEIVE COMMERCIAL E-MAIL MESSAGES FROM TAGGED, AND ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT THEIR EMAIL ADDRESSES AND OTHER PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE USED BY TAGGED FOR THE PURPOSE OF INITIATING COMMERCIAL E-MAIL MESSAGES.

### G) Member Account and Password

Once Member registers for Tagged, Member will have a password and an account with Tagged. Member is responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of Member's password and account. Furthermore, Member is entirely responsible for any and all activities that occur under Member's account. Member agrees to immediately notify Tagged of any unauthorized use of Member's account or any other breach of security known to Member.

### H) Tagged Gold

You may purchase currency for use solely on the Tagged Site ("Tagged Gold"). Tagged Gold is redeemable only on the Tagged site for Tagged digital merchandise and content. Tagged Gold does not expire. Tagged Gold is non-refundable. Tagged Gold has no monetary value. Tagged Gold is not transferable or assignable.

### I) VIP Membership

You may decide to upgrade your membership to VIP status for an additional monthly cost. For details on pricing and what it means to be a Tagged VIP, please visit <http://www.tagged.com/vip/details.html>. If you choose to become a Tagged VIP, you will be able to elect to have your membership automatically renewed on a monthly basis by enrolling in the auto-renew program through our partnership with PayPal. If, at any point, you wish to discontinue your VIP membership, you must visit <http://www.tagged.com/vip/cancel.html> and select 'CANCEL' at least 3 days prior to your next schedule automatic payment so that we can process your cancellation properly. 

### J) Copyrights, Trademarks, Patents and Intellectual Property Rights

Member acknowledges that messages, files or other materials ("Content") contained on the Tagged website and within Tagged email messages, and third party advertisements on the website and distributed via email, of a commercial nature and presented to Member by Tagged and the Services, are protected by copyrights, trademarks, service marks, patents or other proprietary rights and laws. Member is permitted to use Tagged Content or third party Content only as expressly authorized by Tagged or the third party advertiser. Member may not copy, reproduce, distribute, or create derivative works from the Tagged Content or third party Content without expressly being authorized to do so by Tagged or the third party advertiser. Member may make a copy of the Tagged Content or third party Content for Member's personal, noncommercial use only, provided that Member keeps all copyright or other proprietary notices intact. Although Tagged does not claim ownership of content that its Member's may provide to Tagged, by providing content to Tagged, Members automatically grant, and represent and warrant that they have the right to grant, to Tagged a worldwide, irrevocable, perpetual, non-exclusive, and fully sublicenseable, license to use, copy, perform, display, and distribute said content.

Tagged respects copyright law and expects Members to do the same. Illegal or unauthorized copying, distribution, modification, public display, or public performance of copyrighted works is an infringement of the copyright holders' rights. If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, or your intellectual property rights have been otherwise violated, please notify Tagged's Agent for Notice of claims of copyright or other intellectual property infringement ("Agent"), at:

Tagged Copyright Agent  
110 Pacific Ave Mall  
Box #117  
San Francisco, CA 94111  

Please provide our Agent with the following Notice:

  1. Identify the copyrighted work or other intellectual property that you claim has been infringed;
  2. Identify the material on Tagged that you claim is infringing, with enough detail so that we may locate it on the website;
  3. A statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law;
  4. A statement by you declaring under penalty of perjury that (a) the above information in your Notice is accurate, and (b) that you are the owner of the copyright interest involved or that you are authorized to act on behalf of that owner;
  5. Your address, telephone number, and email address; and
  6. Your physical or electronic signature.

Tagged's Agent will forward this information to the alleged infringer. It is Tagged's policy to terminate the accounts of repeat infringers. 

### K) Disputes

The Agreement shall be governed by, and construed in accordance with, the laws of the State of California, without regard to its conflict of law provisions. You and Tagged agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located within San Francisco County, California to resolve any dispute arising out of the Agreement or the Tagged Services. If there is a dispute between participants on this site, or any third party, Tagged is under no obligation to become involved. In the event that Member has a dispute with one or more members, Member hereby releases Tagged, their officers, employees, agents and successors in rights from claims, demands and damages (actual and consequential) of every kind or nature, known or unknown, suspected and unsuspected, disclosed and undisclosed, arising out of or in any way related to such disputes and / or our service. If Member is a California resident, Member waives California Civil Code Section 1542, which says "A general release does not extend to claims which the creditor does not know or suspect to exist in his favor at the time of executing the release, which, if known by him must have materially affected his settlement with the debtor. EACH OF THE PARTIES HEREBY KNOWINGLY, VOLUNTARILY AND INTENTIONALLY WAIVES ANY RIGHT IT MAY HAVE TO A TRIAL BY JURY IN RESPECT OF ANY LITIGATION (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ANY CLAIMS, COUNTERCLAIMS, CROSS-CLAIMS, OR THIRD PARTY CLAIMS) ARISING OUT OF, UNDER OR IN CONNECTION WITH THIS AGREEMENT. FURTHER, EACH PARTY HERETO CERTIFIES THAT NO REPRESENTATIVE OR AGENT OF EITHER PARTY HAS REPRESENTED, EXPRESSLY OR OTHERWISE, THAT SUCH PARTY WOULD NOT IN THE EVENT OF SUCH LITIGATION, SEEK TO ENFORCE THIS WAIVER OF RIGHT TO JURY TRIAL PROVISION. EACH OF THE PARTIES ACKNOWLEDGES THAT THIS SECTION IS A MATERIAL INDUCEMENT FOR THE OTHER PARTY ENTERING INTO THIS AGREEMENT.

### L) Termination

Either party may terminate use of the Tagged website or the Services with or without cause at any time and effective immediately upon written notice to the other party. Tagged may terminate with or without cause at any time and effective immediately, at Tagged's sole discretion, including but not limited to Member's failure to conform with these terms and conditions of the Agreement. Tagged shall not be liable to Member or any third party for termination of use of Tagged or the Services. Member's right to use Tagged or the Services shall cease immediately. Member shall have no right and Tagged will have no obligation thereafter to forward any unread or unsent messages to Member or any third party. Sections G-N shall survive termination of the Agreement.

### M) DISCLAIMERS OF WARRANTIES

MEMBER AGREES THAT USE OF THE TAGGED WEBSITE AND THE SERVICES IS ENTIRELY AT MEMBER'S OWN RISK. THE TAGGED WEBSITE AND THE SERVICES ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND. ALL EXPRESS AND IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT OF PROPRIETARY RIGHTS ARE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMED TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, TAGGED DISCLAIMS ANY WARRANTIES FOR THE SECURITY, RELIABILITY, TIMELINESS, ACCURACY, AND PERFORMANCE OF THE TAGGED WEBSITE AND THE SERVICES. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, TAGGED DISCLAIMS ANY WARRANTIES FOR OTHER SERVICES OR GOODS RECEIVED THROUGH OR ADVERTISED ON THE TAGGED WEBSITE OR THE SERVICES ACCESSED THROUGH ANY LINKS ON THE TAGGED WEBSITE. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, TAGGED DISCLAIMS ANY WARRANTIES FOR VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS IN CONNECTION WITH THE TAGGED WEBSITE OR THE SERVICES. Some jurisdictions do not allow the disclaimer of implied warranties. In such jurisdictions, the foregoing disclaimers may not apply to you insofar as they relate to implied warranties.

### N) LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL TAGGED BE LIABLE ON ACCOUNT OF MEMBER'S USE OR MISUSE OF THE TAGGED WEBSITE OR THE SERVICES, WHETHER THE DAMAGES ARISE FROM USE OR MISUSE OF THE TAGGED WEBSITE OR THE SERVICES, FROM INABILITY TO USE THE TAGGED WEBSITE OR THE SERVICES, OR THE INTERRUPTION, SUSPENSION, MODIFICATION, ALTERATION, OR TERMINATION OF THE TAGGED WEBSITE OR THE SERVICES. SUCH LIMITATION SHALL ALSO APPLY WITH RESPECT TO DAMAGES INCURRED BY REASON OF OTHER SERVICES OR PRODUCTS RECEIVED THROUGH OR ADVERTISED IN CONNECTION WITH THE TAGGED WEBSITE OR THE SERVICES OR ANY LINKS ON THE TAGGED WEBSITE, AS WELL AS BY REASON OF ANY INFORMATION OR ADVICE RECEIVED THROUGH OR ADVERTISED IN CONNECTION WITH THE TAGGED WEBSITE OR THE SERVICES OR ANY LINKS ON THE TAGGED WEBSITE. THESE LIMITATIONS SHALL APPLY TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW. In some jurisdiction, limitations of liability are not permitted. In such jurisdictions, the foregoing limitation may not apply to you.

### O) Indemnification

Member agrees to indemnify and hold Tagged, its subsidiaries, affiliates, successors, assigns, directors, officers, agents, employees, service providers, and suppliers harmless from any dispute which may arise from a breach of terms of this Agreement. Member agrees to hold Tagged harmless from any claims and expenses, including reasonable attorney's fees and court costs, related to Member's violation of this Agreement.

### P) Governing Law

This Agreement and the relationship between Member and Tagged shall be governed by the laws of the State of California without regard to its conflict of law provisions. If any provision of the Agreement is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, the parties nevertheless agree that the court should endeavor to give effect to the parties' intentions as reflected in the provision, and the other provisions of the Agreement remain in full force and effect. Member agrees that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim or cause of action arising out of or related to use of Tagged, the Services or the Agreement must be filed within one (1) year after such claim or cause of action arose or be forever barred. Tagged makes no representation that materials on this web site are appropriate or available for use in other locations, and accessing them from territories where its contents are illegal is prohibited. Those who choose to access this site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with applicable laws.

### Q) Agreement

The Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between Member and Tagged and governs your use of Tagged and the Services, superseding any prior agreements between Member and Tagged. You also may be subject to additional terms and conditions that may apply when you use affiliate services, third-party content or third-party software. The failure of Tagged to exercise or enforce any right or provision of the Agreement shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. The section titles in the Agreement are for convenience only and have no legal or contractual effect.

### Contacting Tagged

Users with questions about this Terms of Service and any of the aforementioned statements may contact Tagged Tagged.com, 110 Pacific Ave Mall, Box #117, San Francisco, CA 94111.

## PRIVACY POLICY

Updated as of June 30, 2010

### User Privacy

Tagged is a fun website that lets you refer your friends to sign up and communicate with each other. Like any website that offers a service where you register and provide information about yourself or your opinions, it is wise to pay attention to your personal information. At Tagged we understand this, and have established this Privacy Policy to explain how information is collected on our website, and how this information is used. Members Must Be 13 years of age or older. Tagged is intended solely for use by persons 13 years of age or older. All persons under 13 are prohibited from registering on Tagged.

### How Does Tagged Protect Children's Privacy?

The safety and privacy of children is extremely important to us.

Tagged is a general audience web site that complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Our registration process is designed to restrict children under the age of 13 from becoming members of Tagged and using our site. We've also designed the tone and style of the site to appeal to teenagers. If we receive information suggesting that a user who has registered with Tagged is under the age of 13, we require the user to provide evidence confirming that the user is at least 13 years old. If the user fails to provide such information within 48 hours, we immediately terminate the user's account and nullify all personally identifiable information displaying on the site and collected from such user.

### What Is the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act?

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) requires that commercial web sites obtain parental consent (under most circumstances) prior to the collection of any personally identifiable information from children whom they know to be under the age of 13. In addition, COPPA requires that web sites that collect personal information from children under the age of 13 provide parents with:

  * Notice. Parents must be provided notice regarding what information is collected, how the information will be used, and with whom the information may be shared.
  * The ability to prevent further use of the information collected about the child and prevent any future collection of personal information from the child.
  * The ability to access and review their child's personal information.

COPPA also limits the amount of personal information a web site can collect from a child. Web sites may not collect any more personal information than is necessary to participate in a given game or activity. 

For more information about COPPA, please visit the [Federal Trade Commission's web site](http://www.ftc.gov/).

Parents: If your child is under the age of 13 and has joined Tagged using a false age, please notify Tagged Tagged Site & Safety Squad at [parentcare@tagged.com](mailto:parentcare@tagged.com), and we will immediately cancel your child's account and nullify all personally identifiable information displaying on the site and collected from them. If you would like to know more about our site, information practices, stored information about your child, or how to close your child's account, please contact Tagged by sending a letter to Tagged.com, 110 Pacific Ave Mall, Box #117, San Francisco, CA 94111. We will happily respond to all letters from parents with Privacy questions or concerns.

### User Information Collected by Tagged

### Personally Identifiable User Information

All users begin using Tagged's services by registering on the Tagged website. When registering, users provide personally identifiable information, which includes their first and last name, email address, mailing address, which school they attend, a user-chosen password, and date of birth, and other personal information. During registration, users also complete survey questions that provide information that is helpful for us to understand the demographics and consumer behavior of our users, such as identifying the users' eye color, style, personality type, favorite color, sport, food, activity or TV show, post-graduation plans or graduation year. Users are also asked to select "Tags" related to their talents, or complete a questionnaire for their online profile, which includes a variety of questions about the user's interests. Users may also provide journal entries to an online journal. To complete the registration process, Tagged sends a validation email message to each user, with a URL link back to our website. This URL contains an alphanumeric identifier and a user-specific numeric passcode that allows us to confirm the user's identity.

### Cookies and Passive Data Collection

Tagged logs standard user information and clickstream data for all users, including a user's IP address, operating system, and page views. When users visit particular pages within Tagged, a UserID may be placed in the URL, allowing customized features for the user. Users should be aware that other websites visited before entering Tagged might place personally identifiable information within a user's URL during a visit to their website, and Tagged has no control over such websites. Accordingly, some of this information may be logged by a subsequent website that collects URL information. In addition to the standard log information, Tagged uses a variety of technologies to create a more personalized experience for its users. Cookies are small data files sent by websites to a user's browser and hard drive that identify the computer to the website. We use cookies to allow enhanced features, such as allowing registered users to bypass typing their passwords before entering the website. We may also use cookies to enable customizable content for users, as they become available. Users have the option, within their Internet browsers, to disable cookies and continue to access the Tagged website. Pixel tags are tiny graphic files that are included in HTML-encoded e-mail messages. We use pixel tags to gather information about the e-mails we send to our registered users. When such a message is opened in an HTML-capable e-mail program, the recipient's computer accesses our server to retrieve the pixel tag file, and allows us to record and store the date and time, the recipient's e-mail address, and other standard logging information. The pixel tag also may read cookies. Tagged web pages may also contain similar pixel tags that allow us to count users who have visited those pages, to compile aggregated statistics about site usage, and to deliver co-branded services as they become available. Tagged pixel tags collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the pixel tag resides. Tagged web pages may also contain pixel tags placed there by third party ad servers, to monitor the effectiveness of their advertising. We do not have access to, nor control over, advertisers' cookies or how they may be used. If you would like more information about advertisers' use of cookies, and about your option not to accept these cookies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

### Document Retention Schedule

All personal information collected by Tagged in connection with your use of the Tagged website, including, without limitation, your name, location, email address, pictures, friend connections, messages, comments, login information, ip addresses and other data, will be stored by Tagged indefinitely in a safe and secure manner.

### How Tagged Uses the User Information

### Personally Identifiable Information

Tagged uses personally identifiable user information for the purposes of the Tagged website, the Tagged referral and friend list building. Personally identifiable information including members' pictures and names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction on Tagged. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join Tagged and to add users to members' friends' networks. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, Tagged allows users to search for other members using first and last name, email address, location and schools where users may have attended. We also use email addresses to send useful information to all registered users regarding the Tagged website.For example, we use email addresses of users, and of those persons provided on their referral lists, to send an invitation to the referred friend and encourage them to sign up on Tagged. When a user lists an email address on the referral page, an email is automatically sent from that registered user to the referral address, encouraging the referral to sign up on the Tagged website. If the referred person does not sign up within a few days, we also send a reminder from the registered user to the referral address. All registered users will be able to view other users Stats, Profiles, Journals and friend list pages, which may include personal information and responses to survey questions. From time to time, Tagged may share the email address and/or other personally identifiable information of any registered user with third parties for marketing purposes. In addition, Tagged may share a registered user's email address with third parties to target advertising and to improve user experience on Tagged's pages in general.

### Cookies and Passive Data Collection

Tagged uses cookie, IP address, clickstream and URL information to improve the content of the Tagged website, the quality of Tagged servers, and to provide enhanced features to users, where available. We use cookies to save UserIDs, session validators, and on users' browsers and hard drives, and may use them to provide tailored products or services to those users, as they become available. We also cross-match user information with information collected from cookies and clickstream data in order to test features of the Tagged website, and to better personalize our various offerings for users. IP Addresses also help us to diagnose problems with our server, to administer the Tagged site, and to otherwise provide the Tagged service to its users. IP addresses may be disclosed to a third party if we believe in good faith that the law or legal process so requires, or to protect the rights or property of Tagged or others. From time to time we may extend various offers from various partner companies, including news or additional details on products and services. A user's usage history may result in specifically tailored special offer screens or products. We may also produce aggregate reports for advertisers. For example, we may report to advertisers the number of users who clicked on an ad, or the number of users that visited different portions of the Tagged website. This information will not include personally identifiable information about a user, or a specific user's online usage patterns.

### Profile Information

Tagged allows Members to provide information to a profile and/or journal entries that is accessible to other users. We use this profile information for the purposes of providing our services to you, such as to analyze demographics, to better personalize our various offerings for users, or to enable other users to find your profile. All information, including any personally identifiable information, which is disclosed by users in his or her public profile and journal entries are available for others to see. Please do not post direct contact information in either your profile or your journal, such as your email addresses, URLs, instant messenger IDs, phone numbers, full names, or addresses. We also caution you not to share sensitive information (such as social security numbers, credit card numbers, and driver's license numbers) with other users whom you do not know or place such information in your profile.

### Invitations

The Invite Friends feature is an easy way for Tagged users to invite friends through email. The email address(es) that you supply to use this service will only be used to send invitations to connect with you on Tagged.

### Surveys and Contests

At various times we may offer surveys or contests to users. Surveys may ask for contact, demographic or unique identifying information to increase the value of the results. Contests may require contact information or other demographic or personally identifiable information in order to determine eligibility. Tagged may use information collected from surveys and contests for the entertainment of users, and to determine, notify and contact winners of various contests. In addition, users' demographic and/or personally identifiable information and responses to survey and contest questions may be used by Tagged and/or shared with third parties in order to provide specifically tailored special offers or advertisements. Tagged will not share a user's email address with third parties unless the user specifically opts-in to such sharing during the completion of or registration for a survey or contest.

### Third Party Links and Ad Servers

Please be aware that links to third party websites and third-party ad server advertisements that are found on Tagged may, or may not, use cookies, pixel tags and web tags. Tagged may provide links to third party websites, which may, or may not, use cookies, pixel tags and web tags. Ad servers may also use these tools to compile information about where users saw particular advertisements, and to determine which ads were clicked on. We are not responsible for, or have any control over, the privacy policies of those third party websites and ad servers, and encourage all users to read the privacy policies of each and every website visited when linking directly from Tagged.

### Protection of Tagged and Others

Tagged may disclose personally identifiable user information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. Tagged may also disclose information about its users to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms of Service; respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-parties; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Tagged, its users or the general public.

### Security

Tagged uses industry standard security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Although we make good faith efforts to store the information collected by the Tagged website in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security. Further, while we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.

### Updating or Removing User Information

As a registered user, you may, at any time, choose to correct or update the information you have submitted to us. This may be done by the following method:

  1. Log in to your Tagged account on our website.
  2. Click the button that says "Update Account Info," under "My Stats."
  3. Change or edit any of the information there, and then click the button at the bottom that says "Update".

As a registered user, you may, at any time, cancel your account by following the instructions set forth here: [ http://help.tagged.com/index.php/account-settings/77-how-do-i-cancel-my-account.html ](http://help.tagged.com/index.php/account-settings/77-how-do-i-cancel-my-account.html)

### Opt-Out

Users can manage their mailing preferences to specify which type of email to opt out of on their Update Account Info page when they are logged in, simply by un-checking the boxes indicating which type of email they would not like to receive. Canceling one's account will also prevent a user from receiving future communications from Tagged, and Tagged will not share the user's information with third parties for marketing purposes. 

### No Spam Policy

We at Tagged.com are opposed to spam. Our No Spam Policy and Terms of Service prohibit all users from engaging in any activity involving spam on our service. Violations of these policies may result in immediate termination of service and legal action against any spammer. Tagged's Terms of Service expressly prohibit users from uploading, posting, emailing, transmitting or otherwise making available junk mail, commercial advertisements, or other form of commercial solicitation on the Tagged website or through Tagged's services. Any violation of our policies, by sending unsolicited email advertisements to or through Tagged.com computer systems, will use or cause to be used Tagged.com servers, located in California. Accordingly, any unauthorized use of Tagged.com computer systems is a violation of our policies and certain federal and state laws, including the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act (18 U.S.C. sect 1030 et seq.), Section 502 of the California Penal Code and Section 17538.45 of the California Business and Professions Code. Such violations may subject the sender and his or her agents to civil and criminal penalties.

### Other Disclosures

### Change of Ownership

In the event of a change in ownership, or a direct merger or acquisition with another entity, we reserve the right to transfer all of Tagged's user information, including email addresses and postal addresses, to a separate entity. All registered users will be notified of any change in ownership, merger or acquisition of Tagged's assets by a third party, and may choose to modify any of their registration information at that time.

### Revisions to This Policy

Tagged reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted on the website, and a user's continued use of Tagged will signify agreement to such changes.

### Contacting Tagged

Users with questions about this Privacy Policy and any of the aforementioned statements may contact Tagged by sending a letter to Tagged.com, 110 Pacific Ave Mall, Box #117, San Francisco, CA 94111.

**USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE PRIVACY POLICY.**

Effective Date September 28, 2010.

Online Safety >>
